{
    "subject": "resource/Vazha-Pshavela",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Host_and_Guest",
    "human_readable": "Vazha Pshavela's notable work is 'Host and Guest'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9388115406036377,
            "question": "Name a notable work by Vazha Pshavela."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8513222932815552,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a famous work by Vazha Pshavela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7020220756530762,
            "question": "What kind of work is 'Host and Guest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726458668708801,
            "question": "What is the title of the work attributed to Vazha Pshavela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6049900650978088,
            "question": "What is Vazha Pshavela best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5255401134490967,
            "question": "What is a famous piece of writing by Vazha Pshavela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4950527846813202,
            "question": "Who authored the work 'Host and Guest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41787344217300415,
            "question": "Who wrote 'Host and Guest'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33802086114883423,
            "question": "What literary accomplishment is attributed to Vazha Pshavela?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33363181352615356,
            "question": "Which literary piece is associated with Vazha Pshavela?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vazha Pshavela's notable work is 'Host and Guest'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8160_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What literary accomplishment is attributed to Vazha Pshavela?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8160_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who wrote 'Host and Guest'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8160_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who authored the work 'Host and Guest'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8160_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8160_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Vazha-Pshavela authored works such as \"Host and Guest,\" among others, thus supporting the statement that Vazha Pshavela's notable work is 'Host and Guest'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}